&gt；&gt；[音乐]
&gt;&gt; [MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们为语言添加了严格模式，因为有一个
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We added a strict mode to the language because there are a
我们想要修复的语言中有很多明显错误的地方。
lot of things in the language that were clearly wrong that we wanted to repair.
但他们将是突破性的变化。
But they would be breaking changes.
所以我们需要某种选择，所以
And so we needed to have some kind of opt in, so
你会说是的，我已经为这可能导致的破坏做好了准备。
you'd say yes, I'm prepared for the breakage this might cause.
因为我想用更好的语言。
Because I want to be using the better language.
我们在详细说明这一点时遇到的困难是，
The difficulty we had in specifying this was,
如何在不引入新语法的情况下使用严格模式？
how do you say I want strict mode without introducing new syntax?
因为我们想要旧的浏览器简单地忽略我们处于严格模式这一事实
Because we wanted older browsers to simply ignore the fact that we're in strict mode
以他们一贯的方式工作。
and work the way they always have.
所以我们花了很多时间试图找出如何做到这一点，并且
So we spent a lot of time trying to figure out how to do that, and
最终，我们想出了一个可怕的黑客。
eventually, we came up with a terrible hack.
我们使用了无用的表达语句，我是
We used the useless expression statement that I was
抱怨早先指定杂注。
complaining about earlier to specify the pragma.
因此，如果函数或文件的第一个语句是字符串，
So if the first statement of a function or a file is the string,
使用Strict；，这会将该文件或该函数置于严格模式。
use strict ;, that puts that file or that function into strict mode.
而在较老的浏览器上，它只是被忽略了，什么也不做，所以这是可行的。
And on older browsers, it's simply ignored and does nothing, so that works out.
我们有文件表格，如果你在Node上，这是很好的。
We've got the file form, which is good if you're on Node.
如果您使用的是浏览器，我建议您只使用函数表单。
If you're on a browser, I recommend you only use the function form.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：原因
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: The reason for
也就是说，Steve Souders会告诉您将所有文件连接在一起。
that is Steve Souders will tell you to concatenate all of your files together.
这意味着您的所有文件都将具有与第一个文件相同的严格程度
And that means that all of your files will have the same strictness as the first
文件，这可能在很多方面都是不好的。
file, and that could be bad in any number of ways.
因此在浏览器中，我们建议您只使用函数形式。
So in browsers, we recommend you only use the function form.
严格模式添加了许多新的保留字。
Strict mode adds a number of new reserved words.
到目前为止
So far,
我只知道在该语言的下一个版本中使用了let和YOUTER。
I'm only aware of let and yield being used in the next edition of the language.
其他版本可能会也可能不会在其他版本中使用。
The others may or may not be used in other editions.
这是严格模式提供的内容列表。
This is the list of things that are provided by strict mode.
不幸的是，这是一个无聊的清单。
Unfortunately, it's a boring list.
所以我只想看看无聊的单子。
So I'm just gonna read the boring list.
函数中不再有隐含的全局变量。
There are no more implied global variables within functions.
这是JavaScript中的一个巨大的设计错误。
This was a huge design error in JavaScript.
所以现在如果您忘记在函数中声明变量，
So now if you forget to declare a variable in a function,
这将是一个语法错误。
it's gonna be a syntax error.
它不会默认为全局变量。
It's not going to default to global variables.
所以这很好。
So that's good.
这不再通过函数形式绑定到全局对象。
This is no longer bound to the global object by the function form.
因此，如果您将方法作为函数调用，则会将其绑定到未定义的和
So if you call a method as a function, this will get bound to undefined and
不是全局对象。
not the global object.
事实证明，这对安全非常重要。
That turned out to be really important for security.
call和apply方法不再默认为全局对象。
The call and apply methods no longer default to the global object.
以前如果调用Apply方法并传入null或undefined，
So it used to be if you called the apply method and passed in null or undefined,
意思是你不想让这个绑定到任何东西，JavaScript会走，你不能
meaning you don't want this to get bound to anything, JavaScript will go, you can't
意思是，你可能指的是全局对象，并会进行替换。
mean that, you probably mean the global object and would do that substitution.
它不再那样做了。
It doesn't do that anymore.
我们去掉了WITH语句。
We got rid of the with statement.
如果您尝试分配给不可写的内容，
If you try to assign to something which is not writeable,
现在您将抛出一个异常。
you will now throw an exception.
它过去常常悄无声息地失败，这对完整性非常不利。
It used to fail silently, which is really bad for integrity.
因为代码可能已经做了更改，
Because the code may have made a change,
假设它成功地进行了更改，并且如果更改失败并且
assuming that it succeeded in making the change, and if the change failed and
如果没有通知，则可能会变得不一致。
it isn't notified, then it could become inconsistent.
我们在删除不可配置属性时也做了类似的事情。
We did a similar thing with deleting non-configurable properties.
我们对求值进行了限制。
We put restrictions on eval.
这周我根本没有谈论过eval，我也不会这样做。
I haven't talked at all this week about eval, and I'm not going to.
Eval是该语言中最易被滥用的特性，我不推荐使用它。
Eval is the most misused feature of the language, and I don't recommend using it.
它在旧语言中的实现真的很可怕，
And the implementation of it in the old language was really quite horrible,
它给了给它一根绳子的人极大的力量。
that it gave extreme powers to whoever provided a string to it.
所以我们对eval做了一些限制。
And so we put some limits on eval.
我抱怨的事情与争论奇怪地联系在一起
The thing I complained about with arguments getting bound strangely to
参数，已经修复了。
the parameters, that's been fixed.
我们摆脱了arguments.caller和arguments.calllee。
We got rid of arguments.caller and arguments.callee.
而且摆脱这些令人惊讶的困难，因为arguments.caller
And getting rid of those was surprisingly difficult because arguments.caller had
从来没有进入过标准。
never been in the standard.
因此，我们不能简单地转到某一行标准并将其删除。
So we couldn't simply go to a line of the standard and delete it.
相反，我们必须将调用者添加到语言中，然后毒害它。
Instead, we had to add caller to the language and then poison it.
我们去掉了八进制文字，因为我们发现它们对人类来说是混淆的。
We got rid of octal literals because we found that they are confusing to humans.
学校里的大多数人都知道数字前面的前导零
Most people in school learned that a leading zero in front of a number
并不重要。
is not significant.
但JavaScript说它是，并把你变成了基数8。
But JavaScript said it was and turned you into base eight.
所以我们解决了这个问题，这让我们从Node社区收到了很多抱怨。
So we fixed that, and that got us a lot of complaints from the Node community.
显然Node的家伙还在使用八进制文字
Apparently that the Node guys are still using octal literals for
正在设置文件权限。
setting file permissions.
我不知道有人还在做这件事，但他们确实在做。
I didn't know anybody was still doing that, but they are.
所以是的，6又加入了八进制，但以一种稍微不那么可怕的方式。
So yes, 6 added octal back in, but in a slightly less awful way.
然后在对象文字或中重复名称
And then duplicate names in an object literal or
函数参数现在语法错误。
function parameters are now syntax error.
所以，如果你说功能食品是逗号，
So, if you say function food a comma a,
现在它将认识到第二个a是一个错误。
it will now recognize that the second a is an error.
我们修复了new运算符，因此忘记了使用new前缀
We fixed the new operator, so forgetting to use the new prefix
在严格模式下，现在将抛出一个异常，而不是默默地重击全局变量。
in strict mode will now throw an exception and not silently clobber global variables.
所以这很好。
So that's good.
我们知道有一些东西因为严格模式而中断了。
There are a few things that we know did break because of strict mode.
例如，如果在浏览器中调用addEventListener
For example, if you call addEventListener in a browser intending
向Window对象添加事件，意外地在旧语言中起作用。
to add an event to the window object, that accidentally worked in the old language.
它意外工作的原因是在浏览器中，
And the reason it accidentally worked was in the browser,
窗口对象是全局对象。
the window object is the global object.
只是碰巧是一回事。
They just happen to be the same thing.
当您将函数作为函数调用时，它将绑定到全局
And when you call a function as a function, this gets bound to the global
对象，它恰好是窗口对象，所以它起作用了。
object, which happens to be the window object, so it worked.
它从来没有打算起作用，它只是意外地起作用了。
It was never intended to work, it just accidentally worked.
所以现在严格模式下，你必须明确。
So now in strict mode, you have to be explicit.
如果你想添加一个事件监听器到窗口，你必须说窗口点。
If you want to add an event listener to the window, you have to say window dot.
语言中没有任何内容可以告诉您是否处于严格模式或
There is nothing in the language that will tell you if you are in strict mode or
如果严格模式可用，但您可以编写这些小函数中的任何一个，
if strict mode is available, but you can write either of these little functions,
他们会准确地告诉你需要知道的。
and they will tell you exactly what you need to know.
严格模式的设计是由JSLint告知的，它们并不完全相同
The design of strict mode was informed by JSLint, they're not entirely the same
因为JSLint强制执行静态分析，并且
because JSLint has forced to do a static analysis and
严格模式可以动态地做一些事情。
strict mode can do some things dynamically.
但如果你正在使用JSLint，并且你应该使用，
But if you're using JSLint, and you should,
那么你应该对严格模式非常满意。
then you should be very happy with strict mode.
我们所做的许多工作都是由mashup的问题引起的。
A lot of the work that we did was motivated by the problems of mashups.
mashup是您获得代表两方的代码的地方，它们希望
A mashup is where you've got code representing two parties that wants to
在同一个页面中协同工作，使用户受益，而不需要
work together in the same page for the benefit of the user without one
能够腐蚀另一个人，这是一个非常困难的问题。
being able to corrupt the other, and that turns out to be a very difficult problem.
所以我们没有一个完整的解决方案，
So we don't have a complete solution to that,
但我们正在解决这个问题的道路上。
but we are on the road to solving that.
所以我们放入语言中的mashup解决方案的设计
So the design of the mashup solutions that we put into the language
来自Google的Caja项目和我自己的Adsafe项目。
were derived from Google's Caja project and my own ADsafe project.
通过修复一些东西，比如这个和
And by fixing things, like the binding of this and
其他一些问题，我们现在可以得到安全解决方案，
some of the other problems, we can now get security solutions,
它们提供了这两者的所有好处，这应该是一件好事。
which provide all the benefits of both of these, which should be a good thing.
那么关于ES5的任何东西有什么问题吗？
So any questions about any of the stuff about ES5?
或者任何关于今天的事情，或者
Or anything about anything today, or
什么都没有？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：只是
anything at all? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Just
在讨论中，我们都在谈论ES6之类的东西，但是。
in the discussion, we're all talking about ES6 and stuff like that, but.
我们会在第三天到达ES6。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，就是这个，是的。
We'll get to ES6 on the third day. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, that's what the, yeah.
你在日程表里有，所以。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好的，
You had that in the schedule, so. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Okay,
还有其他人吗？&gt；&gt；演讲者3：当你谈到如何
anybody else? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: When you talked about how
无处不在的某些构造在网络中存在，并且
pervasive certain constructs are out in the web and
算出它的破损程度和诸如此类的东西，
figure out how much it break and stuff like that,
你是如何收集这些指标的？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这真的很难，
how did you gather those metrics? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It's really hard,
有些只是，我觉得有人做了什么。
some of it was just, I think somebody did something.
我听说有个人做了些什么。
I heard about a guy who did something.
很多是这样的，其中一些是挖掘谷歌代码。
A lot of it was that, some of it was mining Google code.
微软也有一个广泛的代码数据库，我们将针对这一点进行挖掘。
Microsoft also had an extensive database of code, and we would mine against that.
我不确定我们的工具在所有情况下是否有效，因为有些
I'm not confident how effective our tools were in all cases because some of
我们要寻找的模式真的很复杂。
the patterns we're looking for are really complex.
而且有些代码编写得非常糟糕，您可能不一定能够识别
And some code is so badly written that you might not necessarily be able to recognize
模式。
the patterns.
但我们尽了最大的努力，
But we tried as much as was possible,
考虑到现有的技术可以将内容与网络所做的事情相匹配。
given the technology available to match stuff against what the web was doing.